Hello Hello
Guys Welcome to Zero Aasman When we will
discuss about it inside in this video
Bandhan Bank is today at 5.5 percent
we have seen a decline it has been
one of the top losers near Bandhan Bank
so see it was continuously going upwards for 24 days, a
continuous obscene increase was seen in
this suddenly we have seen such a huge decline
so let us see
where it will stop now that is the decline has started
you have the support of the War was
strong supporter of the Guru's
arrest settlements we will try to support the ad then we will
give you target we will
discuss the fear we will tell you step by step
you will see till the end if you like it then
apply if you do not like it at all then like this so
let's start in Bandhan Bank
if we look at the
top here if we look at the present if we see the
top here we see the
top 30 feet in print here ad since then
we have seen a continuous decline and
bottom day is haunted ₹15 here gas
is down and after taking support from here
again  The stop kept moving upwards,
birthday from here watch this channel from 1st
October Khar month towards till 8th October, a
good increase in this problem was
seen throughout and today on Monday this
market is facing a decline in the
office but we are
taking out 2012 in strong support, here
is a very strong support and there
is a fall in Nifty so
now it can slowly come down to here from 115, there is a
lot of spoil sport here, so it
can stop it, if it breaks down even then, if it
breaks down then
a good fall will be seen
but the chances are that it will remain here,
you people write here to-do, it
respects a lot that the tree of Dubai
realized that firstly this happened,
behind Gurjar sold forest land,
so it definitely needs to be tested again,
see here it broke down
for testing again, after that it went up, so this
always happens when anywhere
you see here gangsters
supporting Bigg Boss, right behind,  While taking it, look here
we will show you this, see the break, again the
support is below taking it, proper
support here but it is very good again the
mobile term so SIM, similarly here
we should not be afraid, do not panic
because this is coming again for testing first,
testing through trees is also
necessary, so it is coming here for testing,
after 250 here, see,
in the soft you will get to see a good boss battles, we can
take a good target, to
what extent can we take the target on any issue,
what targets can we fight,
for that we will come to the weekly chart
and after coming to the weekly chart we will only
use the branch, so
why, after applying the dance, we will tell you the target
which will be very important in the coming days, the
measurement of the labels it is giving, it
seems to you in one chair,
more than 80 percent of the matter is being
refilled, so
let's write it carefully from here,
then dance plus two is a medium, there is a
combination of both, here the top when we had Rs.
30, end take the reaction from here  After this,
more support was to be formed, that thing is, by
taking a buy of 20%, see the other rs.60 will be our
first, now let's see, here the
passport moved towards the ad, that's why it got
angry and stopped, again taking
support it went up, then reversed but after going there a
double top pattern was formed, the fall in the bank and
when you see a double top item type, there is a
fall, in the dream it goes upwards in the double border, then it is
white, those who
work, if you don't do everything then it is
not formed, technical LIC works a lot, to what extent it is
enough, this
tells you the best technical research indicator, you should see
now, then the
stock has gone down, the last support was at
2015 rupees and look here,
taking support, the chop started licking again, in the
meantime all the support that was there, that is,
50% twenty three percent 42% 332 percent
50%, these two supports and now resistance has been formed, there is
special interest in constipation, by increasing the
support, the support was ahead, then more resistance is formed
in it, by getting this test done,
food is formed, so see now this stop
copper support here  Taking it above the seat percentage, a big
impact on the amount set or else here it
took support, staff30 went to 2%, 20 minutes
dominant, mixing it, it went up,
you gave it to drink, exactly but the percentage
went up, support has been taken on the syllabus, today's date
minute and then let's see tomorrow, tomorrow it is possible by doing two,
here on one I heard that it can
move upwards by taking support from 22% also,
but the chilli on it will be this much, if it
can come up to ₹10, then tomorrow also a little
decline can be seen, and there will be
less chance, it will go upwards after taking support here,
see how this problem
starts to move upwards, then the
stock does not go upwards like this, even while moving upwards directly,
it makes only one fullback, the
second is the fullback, the third is the fullback, high
school math, due to this it
moves upwards by 100 while making a higher formation,
which this top B
is moving here with the condition of the system, here it will
not be ready until it pulls back, do the next dead target like this  Two,
now good is for someone, we will talk about the target, we will keep it for
6 years, first RK will
keep the target from 10:30 Kalp, we have to
take the target in the upper courtyard, so after 433 if we
see the target in this stock, then
we got to see after 433 if
we
see the target then here we will see
Appoint A 73rd, a little bit of money can go up and
down but the target that it is
showing, then you will get to see the resistance, keep
this in mind, then pizza will go, we will
get the target so that there will be profit, maybe that
problem will happen, if we do the rest also then
we will get to see the resistance there, Taluko
understood Pani Puri, if you liked it well then
definitely like and subscribe to this channel
Vijay Kishor
in the video, thank you for watching my video
Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Hua Tha